(Sheldon:)Good morning and welcome
to Science and Society.
(Sheldon:)I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper, BS, MS,
MA, PhD, and ScD.
(Sheldon:)OMG, right?
(Sheldon:)Perhaps that joke was a little
too hippie-dippy for this crowd.
(Sheldon:)All right then, we'll begin
with opening remarks.
(Sheldon:)Miss Rostenkowski,
would you like to start us off
(Sheldon:)by discussing
your assessment
(Sheldon:)of science's responsibility
to society?
(Sheldon:)Sure.
(Bernadette:)I think all branches
of science
(Bernadette:)have to move cautiously
these days.
(Bernadette:)It's not just giant
nuclear weapons
(Bernadette:)that can destroy
the world.
(Bernadette:)As a microbiologist,
I can tell you
(Bernadette:)even the tiniest organisms
can still tear you a new one.
(Howard:)Interesting.
(Howard:)I think what you might need
to know about my colleague
(Howard:)is that though she claims
her field of interest  is tiny organisms,